Guide to the Jean Yeager Papers, 1959-2012
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Jean Yeager papers 1959-2012
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Yeager, Jean
15.0 linear feet Extent: 7,000 Items
Advertising copy writer and artist who managed his own agency, Jean W. Yeager, Inc. based in Dallas, Tex. Later taught at several Waldorf Method institutions; director of the Anthroposophical Society in America. Collection spans the years 1959-2012 and includes correspondence, direct marketing printed materials, print advertisements and recordings of radio and television broadcast commercials and public service messages that document Yeager's career producing advertising primarily for companies based in Texas. Examples of Yeager's original art are also included. Formats include audio- and videocassettes, audio reels and 16mm films. Companies represented include 7-Eleven, Coca-Cola, Frito-Lay, Radio Shack, Republic Health Corporation, Schenley, Southland Corporation, and Sterling Optical. The collection also touches on Yeager's involvement with the Anthroposophical Society and related enterprises, including Waldorf Method schools such as the Kimberton Waldorf School in Detroit. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
RL.01422
Language: Material in English
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
In addition, original audiovisual materials are closed to patron use. Research Services staff need to produce use copies before contents can be accessed.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Jean Yeager Papers were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2012.
Biographical Note
Jean Yeager managed his own agency, Jean W. Yeager, Inc., based in Dallas, Tex. where he created and produced print and broadcast advertising for a number of clients. After winning several industry awards for his work, Yeager left advertising to pursue interests in anthroposophy, relocating to England where he attended and later taught at Emerson College's Center for Social Development. Yager eventually returned to the United States where he became involved in several activities related to anthropsophy and the Waldorf Method of education, serving as Interim Development Director of the Kimberton Waldorf School in Detroit, Mich. and as Managing Editor of Biodynamics magazine. From 1997 until his retirement in 2007 Yeager served as Administrative Director of the Anthroposophical Society in America. [Source: http://www.steinercollege.edu/files/pdf/wa/YeagerBio.pdf]
Collection Overview
Collection spans the years 1959-2012 and includes correspondence, direct marketing printed materials, print advertisements and recordings of radio and television broadcast commercials and public service messages that document Yeager's career producing advertising primarily for companies based in Texas. Examples of Yeager's original art are also included. Formats include audio- and videocassettes, audio reels and 16mm films. Companies represented include 7-Eleven, Coca-Cola, Frito-Lay, Radio Shack, Republic Health Corporation, Schenley, Southland Corporation, and Sterling Optical. The collection also touches on Yeager's involvement with the Anthroposophical Society and related enterprises, including Waldorf Method schools such as the Kimberton Waldorf School in Detroit.
Collection Arrangement
Arranged in the following Series: General Files; Awards; Creative Binder; Scripts; Large-Format Materials; and Audiovisual Materials. Where possible or practical, original folder titles were maintained.
Subject Headings
Yeager, Jean W.; 7-Eleven, Inc.; Anthroposophical Society in America; Coca-Cola Company; Frito-Lay, Inc.; Radio Shack; Southland Corporation; Advertising; Advertising -- History; Advertising -- United States -- History; Advertising agencies; Advertising agencies -- United States; Advertising agencies -- United States -- History; Advertising executives; Advertising executives -- United States; Radio advertising; Radio scripts; Waldorf method of education; Texas; 16mm; Audiocassettes; Brochures; Videocassettes; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
Related Material
Related materials may be found in the following Hartman Center collections:
Adrienne Cohen Papers
Bud Titsworth Papers
Foote, Cone & Belding Communications, Inc. Records
John O'Toole Papers
Joy Golden Papers
Robert S. Smith Papers
and collections within the J. Walter Thompson Company Archives:
Account Files
Albert Stridsberg Papers
Carroll Carroll Papers
Corporation Vertical Files
Jack Hilton Papers
John F. Devine Papers
Lois Gaeta Papers
Maury Holland Papers
New Business Records
Detailed Description of Collection
- General Files, 1970-2012 and undated
  - Advertising samples, undated (Box 1)
  - Clio Awards, 1983 (Box 1)
  - International Broadcasting Awards, 1982 (Box 1)
  - Jean Yeager awards binder (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 1)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 1)
  - Stanford Agency Greatest Hits, undated, (2 folders) (Box 1)
  - Strange Things Happen to Mad Men (script), 2012 (Box 1)
  - Colorado State yearbook (Part of Monotony game), 1970 (Box 2)
- Awards (Physical objects), 1981-1984
  - 7 -Eleven: Operation Thunderbolt (Box 3)
  - Central Louisiana Ad Club (CENLAD): Addy, radio 60 second, 1984 (Box 3)
  - Golden Radio Award, Best regional/national campaign--Cabell's Dairy, The Standford Agency, 1981 (Box 3)
  - K.W. Tunnell Company, Inc., Productivity Triad (Box 3)
  - The Hollywood Radio and Television Society International Broadcasting Award: Southland Corp. Man On The Streets/Ka-Bells/Jumpers, Jean W. Yeager Creative Services, World's Best Radio Series, 1981 (Box 3)
- Creative Binder, 1981-2001 and undated
  - 7-Eleven (Southland Corp.), 1983 and undated (Box 4)
  - Anthroposophical Society, 1993-2001 (Box 4)
  - Avitron Electronics, undated (Box 4)
  - Award--IBA, 1981 (Box 4)
  - Biodynamic Association (Stella-Natura), 1993-1997 (Box 4)
  - Boxing Association of America, 1993 (Box 4)
  - Citijet/Dallas Love Field, 1985 (Box 4)
  - Clini-Therm Corporation, 1985 (Box 4)
  - Clippings, 1985-1991 (Box 4)
  - Community Supported Agriculture, 1992 (Box 4)
  - Drawing Board Greeting Cards, 1985 (Box 4)
  - Final Test, Inc., undated (Box 4)
  - General Hospital of Lakewood, 1984 (Box 4)
  - Gristede's, undated (Box 4)
  - Group Seven Productions, undated (Box 4)
  - Human Dynamics, Inc., undated (Box 4)
  - Kimberton Waldorf School, 1992-1993 (Box 4)
  - Mercury Provident PlC, 1988 (Box 4)
  - Mtech Electronic Banking Division, 1985 (Box 4)
  - Pennsylvania Horticultural Society, 1992 (Box 4)
  - Republic Health Corporation, 1984 (Box 4)
  - School for Spiritual Science in North America, 1996 (Box 4)
  - Sundial Resorts, undated (Box 4)
  - Super Shades/Southland Corp., undated (Box 4)
  - TekCorps, undated (Box 4)
  - Therapist Helper billing service, 1991 (Box 4)
  - Tidel Systems, circa 1980 (Box 4)
  - Weleda, Inc., 1992 (Box 4)
  - Wordsmiths Writing Consultants, undated (Box 4)
- Scripts, 1971-1988 and undated
  - 7-Eleven
    - Annual meeting, undated (Box 5)
    - Sales meeting film modules, undated (Box 5)
  - American Heart Association--BLS modules, 1987-1988, (2 folders) (Box 5)
  - Anderson Clayton Foods
    - Focus on Excellence, 1984 (Box 5)
    - National sales meeting, 1984 (Box 5)
  - Barricini
    - Presentations, 1986 and undated, (2 folders) (Box 5)
    - Sales meetings, 1986 (Box 5)
  - Change Game final version, 1980 (Box 5)
  - Channel Eleven
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 5)
    - Produced scripts, 1984-1985 (Box 5)
    - Produced spotlist, undated (Box 5)
    - Syndication, undated (Box 5)
    - Talent/Writers letter of agreement, 1985 (Box 5)
  - Chief Auto Parts
    - Meeting, 1981 (Box 6)
    - Syndicated research and potential strategy, 1981 (Box 6)
  - Citgo Petroleum Corporation, 1985 achievements and 1986 plans, 1985 (Box 6)
  - Cliches, undated (Box 6)
  - Coca Cola--100th Annversary Show draft #1, 1985 (Box 6)
  - Corporate communication vita--Events, undated (Box 6)
  - Creative advertising--Agreements, 1971 (Box 6)
  - Dick Dole--Speech suggestions, undated (Box 6)
  - Drawing Board, 1986, (4 folders)
    - Smart Retailing Newsletter, 1985, (5 folders) (Box 6)
    - Trade show draft flyer #1, 1986 (Box 6)
  - Fox Photo, undated (Box 6)
  - Gerald McMillan/Radio Broadcasting Trade accounting, 1985 (Box 6)
  - Introduction to CPR Techniques, 1986 (Box 6)
  - Jean W. Yeager Inc. speech book 1, 1985, (2 folders) (Box 6)
  - Jingles, undated (Box 6)
  - Jobs, 1983-1991
    - (Unnumbered), (3 folders) (Box 7)
    - 91-005 (Box 7)
    - 118 (Box 7)
    - 101-167, (6 folders) (Box 7)
    - Jobs book, 1978-1980, (8 folders) (Box 8)
    - Jobs book, 1980-1981, (8 folders) (Box 9)
  - J.W. Yeager registered mail (scripts mailed to himself), 1971 (Box 9)
  - Mailers and miscellaneous
    - Mailers, undated (Box 9)
    - Industry reports, 1978-1980, (2 folders) (Box 10)
    - Scripts and other, 1985 (Box 10)
  - Mr. Gatti's sales meeting, 1984 (Box 10)
  - N.A.B. Stage Show, TM Communications Inc. third draft, 1984, (2 folders) (Box 10)
  - Northern Telecom launch--Meridian, 1985 (Box 10)
  - Note paper, undated (Box 10)
  - Objects, 1980 (Box 10)
  - Occupations, 1979-1980 (Box 10)
  - Originals, 1984 (Box 10)
  - People and props (Box 10)
  - Phone numbers notebook (Box 10)
  - Props, 1983-1988, (1 of 3 folders) (Box 10)
  - Props, 1983-1988, (2-3 of 3 folders) (Box 11)
  - Radio concepts, 1979 (Box 11)
  - Republic Health Corporation, Gift of Sight, 1984 (Box 11)
  - Samples, 1982-1985
    - Index (Box 11)
    - 101-125, (3 folders) (Box 11)
    - 126-158, (6 folders) (Box 12)
    - 159-172, (2 folders) (Box 13)
  - Schenley Industries
    - General, 1987 (Box 13)
    - Audiovisual, 1986 (Box 13)
    - Cruzan Rum: A New Look, undated (Box 13)
    - Scripts, undated (Box 13)
    - World Class, undated (Box 13)
  - Situations, 1978 (Box 13)
  - Snappers (one-liners), 1978 (Box 13)
  - Southland Corporation, 1984-1987
    - 101-102A (Box 13)
    - 103-122, (6 folders) (Box 14)
    - 123 (Box 15)
    - Annual meeting, 1985, (2 folders) (Box 15)
    - Competitive market environment, 1983 (Box 15)
    - Corporate films/Presentation book 101-107, 1984-1986, (2 folders) (Box 15)
    - Development 061683-1, 1983, (2 folders) (Box 15)
    - Flipbook #1 draft 1, 1984 (Box 16)
    - Jobs and payments, 1985 (Box 16)
    - John Thompson letter, 1985 (Box 16)
    - John P. Thompson speeches, 1978-1980, (2 folders) (Box 16)
    - MDA news release, 1983-1984 (Box 16)
    - MDA Sourcebook, undated (Box 16)
    - Motorsport Department, 1986 (Box 16)
    - Notebooks, 1984-1986 (Box 16)
    - Oh Thank Heaven! The Story of Southland Corporation, 1977 (Box 16)
    - Potential names and rationales for Southland Complex, 1983 (Box 16)
    - Sales meeting film, 1985-1986 (Box 16)
    - Southland Show, undated, (2 folders) (Box 17)
    - Store Site Development task force, 1985, (2 folders) (Box 17)
    - Superstore training films, 1983 (Box 17)
  - Texas Dairy Queen, undated (Box 17)
  - Texas 150th birthday Celebration, 1985-1986 (Box 17)
  - TV Concepts, undated (Box 17)
- Large Format Materials
  - Art
    - Flower, undated (Box 18)
    - Point-of-sale cartoons, undated (Box 18)
    - Political designs, 1975 (Box 18)
    - Spirit of 76, 1975 (Box 18)
  - Awards
    - Clio, 1983 (Box 18)
    - International Broadcasting Awards, 1979-1981 (Box 18)
  - Creative Binder
    - The White Agency brochure, undated (Box 18)
  - Name cards, undated (Box 18)
  - Photograph, undated (Box 18)
  - Print advertisements
    - 7-Eleven, undated (Box 18)
    - Adoption public service message, undated (Box 18)
    - Garland Community Hospital/Republic Health Corp., 1984 (Box 18)
    - Gristede's, undated (Box 18)
    - Republic Health Corporation, 1984 (Box 18)
  - Miscellaneous prints (not by Yeager)
    - Last Supper, undated (Box 18)
    - Winnie the Pooh, undated (Box 18)
    - Photograph, Broadcast convention stage (Box 19)
  - Print advertisements and storyboards
    - 7-Eleven, undated (Box 19)
    - Boxing Association of America, 1993 (Box 19)
    - Chief Auto Parts, 1980 (Box 19)
    - Gristede's, 1981 (Box 19)
    - Jeep CJ, undated (Box 19)
    - Liquid Paper, undated (Box 19)
    - Milk (generic), undated (Box 19)
    - Monotony game, Colorado State University Silver Spruce, 1970 (Box 19)
    - National Rare Blood Club, undated (Box 19)
    - Public service messages, 1973-1975 (Box 19)
    - Tidel Systems, 1980 (Box 19)
- Audiovisual Materials, 1959-1992 and undated
  - 20th Century Restaurant--Atlanta. 1983. March 3-5 Mardi Gras [Revised]. Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - 4 Markets--Tags. Undated. Dallas, Austin, San Antonio, Denver. Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - Award Dubs. 1986. AMFAC Hotel & Resort, That AMFAC Jack. Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - Bay Street. Undated. Plano Fishermen, revised. Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - Casa Manana. 1982. Ed Busch Studios Post: Ira Lipson (Reel #1). Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - Casa Manana. 1982. Ed Busch Studios Post: Ira Lipson (Reel #2). Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - Channel 11. 1985. 8 O'clock Movie (Let's Do It Again, Poobah). Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - Channel 11. 1985. 8 O'clock Movies (6 Spots). Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - Channel 11. 1985. Bump Week Best o' West (8 spots). Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - Channel 11. 1985. No-Name Week (4 spots). Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - Circle Washer Leasing. Undated. Jake Wild Lines. Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - Circle Washer Leasing. 1984. Washing Circles. Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - Daily Noon Buffet--Miami. 1983. Sunday Brunch (w/ Music, w/out Music). Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - Dallas Morning News. 1982. Dick Bruiser--Turn Tables. Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - Dallas Morning News. 1982. DMN- 5 Spots. Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - Dallas Morning News. Undated. DMN-Serves. Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - Dallas Morning News. Undated. The Judge, Crazy Ray (:30). Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - Diamond Head Hair Salon. 1983. Diamond Head Leadered At Tail (:60). Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - Doubletree Hotel. 1987. Classic Encounters (:60). Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - Doubletree Hotel. 1987. Teen Club Introduction. Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - Frank: Obsece phone call. 1980. Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - Gemini Music Group, Inc. 1983. Great Performances (:60 Radio). Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - General Hospital of Lakewood. Undated. Podiatry Spots. Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - Innco. Hospitality. 1985. Melon Cauli- Celebration Club and Spirits Club. Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - Ira Lipson. Undated. Heroes. Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - The Gas Appliance Co. Undated. 1. Out of Hat, 2. Disappearing Act, 3. Finger Snap, 4. Cannon. Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - Chateau-Radio. 1959. Grand Cru Classe Margaux- Premium Radio Advertising fron the vineyard of: Jean W. Yeager. Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - Demo A. Undated. Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - Family Fun Syndication. Undated. Demo. Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - Jean W. Yeager, Inc. 1979. '79 Demo/Mr. Balloon. Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - Jean W. Yeager, Inc. 1982-1986. 021 (Jean Yeager, Cox Cable, Gen. Hospital of Lakewood, Radio, Applebees). Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - Jean W. Yeager, Inc. 1986-1987. 022 (Bay Street, Plantation Products, Applebees). Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - Jean W. Yeager, Inc. 1982-1985. 023 (Same Day Surgery, Interstate Battery, Jean Yeager, AMPAC Hotel and Resort, Swensen's). Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - Jean W. Yeager, Inc. 1984. 024 (SWC Basketball, Republic Health Corporation). Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - Jean W. Yeager, Inc. 1984. 1984 Demo. Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - Jean W. Yeager, Inc. 1983. Classic Comedy Fall '83 Demo Master. Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - Jean W. Yeager, Inc. 1982. New Master Demo. Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - Jean W. Yeager, Inc. 1969-1970. The Cold War. Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - Jean W. Yeager, Inc. 1983. Unassuming Comedy Demo. Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - Light Touch. 1983. Mild-Mannered Demo '83. Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - Ms. Café. Undated. Office, Glenn, Donasan's. Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - Nutrisystems. 1982. 8269. Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - Plantation Products. 1986. Health Spa, Taste Test, Stuffing Council, House of Birds. Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - Randolph City Medical Center. 1984. Larry Turner and Karen Smith. Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - Republic Health Corporation. Undated. Podiatry Voire Tracks. Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - RHL. 1984. Dramatic, Dramatic w/Tag, Our Gift, Our Gift w/Tag, Grandchild w/Tag, Cack-A-Racks, Straight. Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - Swensen's Supreme. Undated. Demos :64 sec. Swensen Supreme/Collateral, :60 sec. Version. Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - Swensen's Supreme. 1983. Swensens Ice Cream 1. Loan Officer, 2. Fortune Teller, 3. Fortune Teller w/Svensens, 4. Fortune Teller Take #1. Audio tape reel. (Box 20)
  - [Master]. Undated. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Applebees. 1985. Spyguys (:60 Radio). Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Best of the Stanford Agency. 1979. 16mm film. (Box 21)
  - Best of the Stanford Agency. Undated. 7-Eleven. Audio tape reel. (Box 21)
  - Best of the Stanford Agency. Undated. 1. Coffee Club, 2. Owl & Rooster, 3. Watermelon Sing Along, 4. Beautiful Milk, 5. 2 Old Strange Things, 6. 2 New Strange Things, 7. It's About Time, 8. Soft Drink Interview, 9. Paperback Books, 10. :30 Submarine, 11. Burrito, 12. Big Gulp/Generic. 16mm film. (Box 21)
  - Billy Bob's Song. 1983. Jean W. Yeager and David Eaton. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Brodie Buick. 1983. Car Wars (:60). Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Bump Week. Undated. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Channel 11. 1986. Generic Shell For All Ranger Tags (:60 Radio). Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Channel 11. Undated. SWC Basketball (Jan.2-Jan. 5 Games). Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Channel 11. Undated. The Super Ones: 15 Spots -- 3 Hilarious Campaigns. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Channel 11. Undated. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Channel 11. Undated. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Dallas Morning News. 1982. 5 Spots- Turn Tables/Dick Bruiser/Swish/Silk/Bull. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Dallas Morning News. Undated. DMN-2173/DMN-2183 Good Sports #2. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Great Performances. 1983. Spring Cleaning Concerto. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Hall & Northway. 1982. Shear Precision. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Hanover Olds. Undated. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Health Care Radio Network. Undated. Wordsmiths- Jean Yeager. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Jean W. Yeager, Inc. 1983. '83 (Swensens, Ms. Café, Heroes(5), Great Perform, Swensens(2)). Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Jean W. Yeager, Inc. Undated. 025 Miscellaneous--Reel 1 (5940-6599). Audio tape reel. (Box 21)
  - Jean W. Yeager, Inc. Undated. 026 Miscellaneous--Reel 2 (6668-6830). Audio tape reel. (Box 21)
  - Jean W. Yeager, Inc. Undated. 027 Miscellaneous--Reel 3 (6882--7066). Audio tape reel. (Box 21)
  - Jean W. Yeager, Inc. 1980-1981. 703 Valencia. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Jean W. Yeager, Inc. 1982. Demo- Prod. MASTER(7:30). Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Jean W. Yeager, Inc. 1985. Family Fun. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Jean W. Yeager, Inc. 1983. Heroes. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Jean W. Yeager, Inc. 1983. Hungry Pelican. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Jean W. Yeager, Inc. Undated. Lucky Phone Call, Jumper Cabells. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Jean W. Yeager, Inc. Undated. Mild Mannered Demo. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Jean W. Yeager, Inc. Undated. Radio Comedy. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Jean W. Yeager, Inc. 1987. Restaurant Radio '87. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Jean W. Yeager, Inc. 1982. Spring '82. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Kimberton W.S. 1991. 50th Anniversary. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Military Stereo & TV. Undated. Buddies #1, Girlfriend #1. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Mother Dubbers, Inc. Undated. Krestmark Radio. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Ms. Café. 1983. Office, Glenn, Donasan's. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Prucare. 1984. 1. Foghorn, 2. Mr. Picker, 3. Mr. Puller Austin. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Radio Shack. Undated. Radio Shack Computer :60's. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Radio TV Reports. Undated. Molson. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Red Robin/Denny's (028). 1987-1988. Audio tape reel. (Box 21)
  - Republic Health Corporation. Undated. Cataracts. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Republic Health Corporation. Undated. Gift of Health. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Restaurant. 1987. 1. Baystreet--Whole Story, 2. McDonald's Salad, 3. Taco Bell--Spiller, 4. Applebee's--154 Oysters, 5. Baystreet--Fisherman. Audio tape reel. (Box 21)
  - Sheraton Century Hotel. Undated. The Coconut Grove. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Southern Union Gas. Undated. Great Gassini-4. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - The Stanford Agency. 1980. 1980 TV Spots. 16mm film. (Box 21)
  - Stars To Go. 1986. No Exaggeration. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Sterling Optical. Undated. :60 Radio Comedy 1. Cocktail Lounge, 2. Cop. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Sterling Optical. Undated. Belly Flop Splash #1. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Sterling Optical. Undated. Eyes Have It- Stereo. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Sterling Optical. Undated. In Their Eyes. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Sterling Optical. Undated. Officer Rich/Mime. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Sterling Optical. 1982. Pinnocio Demo. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Sterling Optical. 1982. Radio Coupon Generic & Florida. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Sterling Optical. Undated. See it in Their Eyes Music cuts. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Sterling Optical. 1982. Show Off #2 Splashs #3. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Sterling Optical. Undated. Show Off Splash #2. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Sterling Optical. 1982. Switchboard Contact Demos. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Sterling Optical. 1983. TV Demo. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Sterling Optical. 1983. TV Demos- Cut A with music, Cut B w/out. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Sterling Optical. 1983. TV/Scratch :32. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Stop N' Go. Undated. Escape Artist, Woody, & Sylvester. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Stop N' Go. Undated. Sumner-Berry-Brown A/Escape Artist, B/Woody, C/Sylvester. Audio tape reel. (Box 21)
  - Summer '82. 1982. Humor Cassette. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Summer '83. 1983. Sample. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Swensen's Supreme. 1983. Demo. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Swensen's Supreme. Undated. Loan Officer/Fortune Teller. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Taco Bell. 1983. Regional Radio '87- Mr. Spiller :60, 49 cents Line-up :30, & Banker's Alike :30. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - The Gas Appliance Co. Undated. 1. Out of Hat, 2. Disappearing Act, 3. Finger Snap, 4. Cannon. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Unknown. Undated. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Unknown. Undated. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Unknown. Undated. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Vabce-Matthews Advertsing. 1987. Casa Manana- 6. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Wango Taco. 1982. 11/17/80 KVIL. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Woodview Regional Hospital. 1980. T-H-E Card. Audiocassette. (Box 21)
  - Various. 1986. All 1986 Spots. VHS. (Box 22)
  - Various. Undated. Prisoners: As A Resource For Social Change. VHS. (Box 22)